In this video, we're going to execute equivalent For loop and While loop code.
在本视频中，我们将执行等效的 For 循环和 While 循环代码。
A for loop is sometimes called syntactic sugar
for 循环有时被称为语法糖，
because it allows you to write a more compact code for counting,
因为它允许你编写更紧凑的计数代码，这是
a common programming idiom.
一种常见的编程习语。
Let's look at their similar anatomy,
让我们来看看它们相似的解剖结构，
both have an initialization statement.
两者都有初始化语句。
In the for loop, it follows the for keyword and then the equivalent while loop,
在 for 循环中，它紧随其后的是 for 关键字，然后
it is just before the beginning of the while loop.
是等效的 while 循环，就在 while 循环开始之前。
The conditional expression is the second piece,
条件表达式是第二部分，紧
following the for keyword and the piece inside parentheses after the while keyword.
随于 for 关键字和 while 关键字之后的括号内的部分。
The increment statement is the third piece
increment 语句是 for
following the for keyword but an equivalent while
关键字之后的第三部分，但是等效的 while
loop would increment inside the loop body just before the close curly brackets.
循环将在循环主体内的右大括号之前递增。
Finally, any statements that happen in the body of the for loop
最后，在 for 循环主体中发生的任何语句
could also happen in a while loop before the increment statement.
也可能发生在 increment 语句之前的 while 循环中。
Let's see these two equivalent loops in action.
让我们来看看这两个等效循环的实际运行情况。
As always, we begin with our execution arrow inside main.
与往常一样，我们从 main 中的执行箭头开始。
We initialize y to one and n to three.
我们将 y 初始化为一，n 初始化为三。
Now, the syntax of the for loop has the int
现在，for 循环的语法在 for
i = 1 initialization just after the for keyword,
关键字之后有 int i = 1 的初始化，
so we'll pause the execution arrow there as the while
所以当
execution arrow on the right enters the open curly brace and initializes i,
右边的 while 执行箭头进入大括号并初始化 i 时，我们将暂停那里的执行箭头，以同样
changing the state of our program in the same way.
的方式改变程序的状态。
The purpose of the curly braces is subtle.
花括号的用途很微妙。
Since scope of variable i is limited to the for loop,
由于变量 i 的作用域仅限于 for 循环，因此
the curly braces restrict the scope of variable i to this box.
花括号将变量 i 的范围限制在该框内。
Otherwise, its scope would be the whole main function
否则，它的作用域将是整个主函数
and it would not be equivalent to the for loop version.
，而不等同于 for 循环版本。查看@@
Looking at the conditional expression,
条件表达式，
we see 1 < 3 is true,
我们看到 1 < 3 是真的，
so we enter the loop and begin executing statements there.
所以我们进入循环并开始在那里执行语句。
Y times i is 1 times 1 which is 1.
Y 乘以 i 是 1 乘以 1 也就是 1。
Next, we'll increment i to 2 and return to the top of the loop.
接下来，我们将 i 递增到 2，然后返回到循环的顶部。
Checking the conditional expression 2 < 3 is true,
检查条件表达式 2 < 3 是否正确，
so we enter the loop and evaluate y times i which is 1 times 2, assigning 2 to y.
因此我们进入循环并计算 y 乘以 i，即 1 乘以 2，将 2 赋给 y。
We'll increment i to 3 and return to the top of the loop,
我们将 i 增量
3 < 3 is false,
为 3 然后返回循环的顶部，3 < 3 为假，
so we move the execution arrow to just after the loop.
因此我们将执行箭头移到循环之后。
Respecting the scope of i in the for loop,
尊重 for 循环中 i 的作用域，
we also exit the curly brace after the while loop,
我们还在 while 循环之后退出大括号，
destroying the box for i since it is now out of scope.
销毁 i 的盒子，因为它现在超出了作用域。
Finally, we return zero and exit main.
最后，我们返回零并退出 main。